const data = [
  {
    id: "1",
    question: "What are accordion components?",
    answer:
      "Accordion components are user interface elements used for organization.",
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    question: "What are they used for?",
    answer:
      "They are commonly employed in various contexts, including FAQs and product descriptions.",
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    question: "Accordion as a musical instrument?",
    answer:
      "The accordion is a musical instrument with a keyboard and bellows that produces sound.",
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    question: "Can I create an accordion component with a different framework?",
    answer:
      "Yes, it is possible to create an accordion component with another framework.",
  },
  {
    id: "5",
    question:
      "What is the difference between an accordion and a tab component?",
    answer:
      "Accordion components show content within a collapsed section, while tabs switch between different sections.",
  },
  {
    id: "6",
    question: "How do I style an accordion component?",
    answer:
      "You can style an accordion component using CSS, applying custom classes, or using a CSS framework.",
  },
  {
    id: "7",
    question: "Can accordions improve user experience?",
    answer:
      "Yes, they help organize content efficiently and reduce clutter, enhancing user experience.",
  },
  {
    id: "8",
    question: "What are the best practices for designing accordions?",
    answer:
      "Ensure that each section is clearly labeled and avoid nesting accordions within accordions.",
  },
  {
    id: "9",
    question: "What is an accordion panel?",
    answer:
      "An accordion panel is the collapsible section within an accordion that contains content.",
  },
  {
    id: "10",
    question: "How can I make my accordion accessible?",
    answer:
      "Use semantic HTML elements and ARIA attributes to ensure that accordions are accessible to all users.",
  },
];

export default data;
